telegraphtoday.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Telegraph Today

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Telegraph Today, (“TT”),  collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.telegraphtoday.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by TT.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, and other identifying information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-Personal Identification Information**

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners may collect various types of information that are anonymous, de-identified or otherwise not intended to personally identify Users whenever they interact with our Site. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of non-personal identification information collected may include: network or Internet protocol address and type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Safari, Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast, Verizon or AT&T), mobile network, device identifiers, advertising identifiers, the web pages of the Site you have visited, sites visited before and after you visit the Site, the type of handheld or mobile device used to view the Site (e.g., iPhone, Blackberry), general location information (e.g., city, county, and/or state), demographics, interests, and the content and advertisements you have accessed, seen, forwarded and/or clicked on.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” or similar technologies to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners also may use cookies or similar technologies to manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Site and/or other networks or sites. This also helps us, our service providers and partners provide more relevant advertising. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How Collected Information May Be Used:**

We, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may use collected information to improve the design and content of our Site, to deliver more relevant marketing messages and advertisements, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and to perform analytics. We also may use this information to analyze usage of our Site or content, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site to personalize user experience. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. Information may be used to run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature, to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them, and to send periodic emails. We may use the email address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. We may use information to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Sites, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy statement.

**Sharing Your Personal Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others.

We may disclose information we have collected from you or the device used to access the Sites in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe in our sole discretion it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our [Terms of Use](https://www.telegraphtoday.com/terms-of-use/), to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.

In addition, we may transfer information if we, or one of our business units, are acquired by, sold to, merged with or otherwise transferred to another entity.

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Opt-out**

If you would like to opt-out of having your information anonymously collected for marketing research you can download the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

TT has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and Terms of Use. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Telegraph Today  
638 Camino De Los Mares  
Ste H130  
San Clemente, CA 92673  
support@telegraphtoday.com

This document was last updated on April 24, 2015.
